The menu of the food corner of Sanrio
Puroland
Wow!
It's so cute!
It's a present from Daniel
Daniel and Kitty's curry
Mayumero's cake
Cinnamon Teriyaki Chicken Pao
White chocolate drink
Cinnamon drink
It's a drink of Gunga Juice
Wow!
I'm hungry
I want to eat this
I want to eat cinnamon
I want to eat Kitty
I want to eat Daniel
Let's share
I want to take a picture
The desk is pink
Let's eat this
Let's eat
It's cute
It's inside
What is it?
It's a white curry
What does it taste like?
It's a different curry
It looks sweet
It's creamy
Wow!
Kitty is printed on it
It's cute
It's Santa's hat
It's a Christmas tree
It's cute
Let's eat
It's a cake of a cute cat
It's good
It's like a beauty
It's like a cat
Let's eat
I'm embarrassed
Chicken McFlurry!
It tastes like chicken.
The bread is very soft.
It's good because it's in my mouth.
It looks delicious.
I'm sorry.
It's a pity.
There are a lot of ingredients.
Is this cheese?
It's cheese.
Let's eat.
Hmm.
It looks delicious.
It has orange cheese.
It's cheddar cheese.
I see.
Cheese and curry go well together.
It's very delicious.
There are many ingredients including
meat.
It's delicious.
Is it sweet curry?
Yes, it is.
It's sweet.
It's mild and delicious.
I'll eat this.
It has hamburger steak.
I'm sorry to say that.
I'll eat this.
Cheese?
Cheese curry?
It's like a mild curry.
Cheese?
Cheese curry?
No, it's not.
But it's definitely different.
The hamburger is really good.
It's good?
It's good with curry.
What is this mild feeling?
Creamy?
It's creamy curry.
Spicy?
But what is it?
Milk?
It's milky.
It's spicy.
This is not spicy.
This is not spicy at all.
It's like a mild curry.
I think anyone can eat this.
If you like spicy food, you should come
here.
There are various kinds of curry.
I think you can enjoy various ways of
eating.
I think there are many stars.
I think it's Monaka.
Monaka?
I ate Monaka curry earlier.
I'll taste it again.
I'll check it.
I can't taste it.
inferior to
Maybe you can taste it.
I think I can't taste it.
You should try it.
Let's check the smell of this drink.
It's cute that there is a tea bag.
I can smell the ice.
I think there is a tea bag inside.
I think so.
There is a tea bag inside.
It's ice.
I think so.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for watching this video.
It's delicious!
What is this?
It's like drinking white chocolate.
It's cold and milky.
It's delicious.
It's like a cute donut.
It's good.
How is it?
I'll have it.
It's like apple jelly.
Chibu-Chibu!
It's so fun!
The texture is so fun.
It's like a lot of things are coming
in.
It's so delicious and fun.
Look at this!
It's cute!
I'd like to have the most gorgeous
cake.
I like Maymelo-chan's cake because it's
black.
Strawberry!
Wow!
What is this?
Let's eat!
Is it good?
It's good.
When I come to a place like this, I
want to eat a cake.
The strawberry is sweet and sour and
the sponge cake is chewy.
I feel like I'm here just by eating
this.
It's delicious. The taste is also
perfect.
The sponge is fluffy.
It's very fluffy.
The strawberry is also fluffy.
It's delicious.
It's a good size.
All of them are delicious.
There are many menus.
The menu we are eating now is a
Christmas limited menu.
When you come to a place like this,
please try this menu.
Please try it.